Let me just say,
Theo is awake, man.
I don't think we're just sending money to a place.
I do believe that our country's owned by Israel.
What I say, James Lee is a conspiracist
who brands himself as a champion of the independent thought
his commentary distorts the nature of anti-Semitism
and vilifies Jewish communities.
Damn, James.
Well, I challenge them to find an example
of me vilifying a Jewish community, you know?
Yeah, well, it says right here,
they aren't even hiding it anymore, Israel owns America.
Well, I mean, that's, they do.
Yeah, you're like, we can't pay our nurses.
We can't, you know, I'm saying we don't have,
like we have issues in our public schools,
more people are choosing to homeschool than ever,
which is just another burden on the family, really, right?
You know, our food supply has been deemed toxic, toxic, right?
That's something that we're battling right now.
70% of young men can't serve in the military
because of the physical shape that they're in, right?
So you start to wonder,
why do we have this extra money to just send to a place, right?
So that, that I think is a very fair question.
And I've been thinking about a lot,
and I do think, I don't think we're just sending money
to a place, I do believe that our country's owned
by Israel and that, so you just give the money to the boss.
So it's not us getting, they're just getting the money
that's, that's, that's, that's theirs, yeah.
That's what I started to relax.
I'm like, yeah, because if you do this for so long
and it doesn't make any, you know what I'm saying?
Like, there's no answer.
It's like, oh, well, that's just,
that's the boss coming and just getting his money.